<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Metaverse on Welcome to my Cv!</title>
        <link>https://example.com/categories/metaverse/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Metaverse on Welcome to my Cv!</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/metaverse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>2. Deverse.Studio</title>
        <link>https://example.com/post/deverse/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/post/deverse/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://example.com/post/deverse/deverse4.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post 2. Deverse.Studio" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;studio-and-team&#34;&gt;Studio and Team&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEVERSE.STUDIO&lt;/strong&gt; is a &lt;strong&gt;METAVERSE-SPECIFIC DESIGN STUDIO&lt;/strong&gt; based in Paris, co-founded by Ariel Claudet and Alessio Scalabrini. The studio specializes in concept, design, and realization of projects within the metaverse, particularly focusing on collaborations with high-end luxury brands on an international level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/ariel-claudet/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARIEL CLAUDET&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is an architect, artist and designer. For the past 10 years, Ariel worked as an Architect for world-renowned award winning studios in Paris, Tokyo, Los Angeles, Amsterdam and for the Government in Haiti.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/alessio-scalabrini-062091b/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;strong&gt;ALESSIO SCALABRINI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a Global Design Director with over 15 years of experience in design, interiors and events ideation and production.
Strong and solid background in delivering innovative concepts that foster meaningful, relevant connections through a design-driven approach. Demonstrated ability to translate global strategies and creative visions into immersive brand experiences and consumer engagements, improving brand perception, increasing brand awareness and driving business value&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-career&#34;&gt;My career&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During my one-year experience at DEVERSE.STUDIO, a metaverse-specific design studio based in Paris co-founded by Ariel Claudet and Alessio Scalabrini, I had the opportunity to work on a range of exciting projects that focused on the intersection of luxury brands and the metaverse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the significant projects I contributed to was the &lt;strong&gt;TELEPERFORMANCE METAVERSE&lt;/strong&gt;, where I was involved in designing and implementing a metaverse shop experience. This project aimed to enhance the customer experience for one of the leading brands in the field. It was fascinating to combine the principles of luxury branding with the immersive capabilities of the metaverse to create a truly unique and engaging shopping experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another project I worked on was the &lt;strong&gt;TOTEM METAVERSE&lt;/strong&gt;, which involved visualizing art within the metaverse. I had the chance to contribute to developing the concept and manifestation of the studio&amp;rsquo;s vision for metaverse applications. It was exciting to explore how art could be presented and experienced in this virtual realm.
Additionally, I played a role in the development of a shopping experience within the metaverse for a &lt;strong&gt;luxury brand&lt;/strong&gt;. This project required creating a compelling storyboard and integrating &lt;strong&gt;NFTs&lt;/strong&gt; linked to the brand&amp;rsquo;s history. It was fulfilling to be part of a team that crafted a narrative-driven experience and utilized innovative technologies like NFTs to enhance the brand&amp;rsquo;s presence in the metaverse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working at &lt;strong&gt;DEVERSE.STUDIO&lt;/strong&gt; provided me with invaluable experience in the emerging field of metaverse-specific design. Collaborating with renowned luxury brands and being involved in cutting-edge projects allowed me to develop a deep understanding of the metaverse landscape and its potential for immersive experiences. I was able to apply my design skills, storytelling abilities, and technological knowledge to create captivating and meaningful metaverse projects.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
