<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Architecture on Welcome to my Cv!</title>
        <link>https://example.com/categories/architecture/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Architecture on Welcome to my Cv!</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/architecture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>2. Golem Studio</title>
        <link>https://example.com/post/golem/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/post/golem/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://example.com/post/golem/golem.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post 2. Golem Studio" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;studio-and-team&#34;&gt;Studio and Team&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GOLEM&lt;/strong&gt; is an architecture, art &amp;amp; design studio founded in 2022 by &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/ariel-claudet/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Ariel Claudet&lt;/a&gt;.
The studio acts on both the digital and the physical realms through various means such as architecture, visual art, stage design, augmented reality and metaverse-specific architecture all reflecting its holistic approach of Design.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://example.com/post/golem/golem_logo.png&#34;
	width=&#34;8006&#34;
	height=&#34;2186&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://example.com/post/golem/golem_logo_hu245e2ce95abf8f580032fd05300464a3_153079_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://example.com/post/golem/golem_logo_hu245e2ce95abf8f580032fd05300464a3_153079_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;GOLEM, Paris FRANCE &#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;366&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;878px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-career&#34;&gt;My career&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During my one-year experience at &lt;strong&gt;GOLEM&lt;/strong&gt;, I had the privilege of contributing to various projects, participating in the concept phase, and realizing architectural drawings and realistic renders. This involvement allowed me to immerse myself in the creative process and witness firsthand the transformation of ideas into tangible architectural desi  gns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One notable project I worked on was the design of a stage inside the &amp;ldquo;Giardino della Marinaressa&amp;rdquo; for the &lt;strong&gt;Venice Biennale&lt;/strong&gt;, in collaboration with the &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://ecc-italy.eu/about/aboutus&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;strong&gt;European Cultural Center&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This project showcased the studio&amp;rsquo;s ability to create engaging and functional spaces within a culturally significant context, demonstrating their expertise in architectural design for art exhibitions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another exciting project I was involved in was the design of an art gallery within the &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Temple of Humanite&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; in &lt;strong&gt;Paris&lt;/strong&gt;, known as Payenne Paris. This unique space was conceived to host temporary exhibitions, providing a platform for artists to showcase their work while integrating seamlessly with the cultural heritage of the site. It was a remarkable experience to be part of a project that combined contemporary art with historical architecture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, I contributed to the concept development of an urban installation for the public in &lt;strong&gt;Los Angeles&lt;/strong&gt;, in collaboration with &lt;strong&gt;Air Jordan&lt;/strong&gt;. This project aimed to create a transformative experience that would revitalize the site and engage with the community. It was inspiring to be part of a team that leveraged design to spark public interaction and revaluation of urban spaces.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
