<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>University on Welcome to my Cv!</title>
        <link>https://example.com/categories/university/</link>
        <description>Recent content in University on Welcome to my Cv!</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/university/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>1. Building Construction Management</title>
        <link>https://example.com/post/muge/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/post/muge/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://example.com/post/muge/muge.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post 1. Building Construction Management" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;univeristy-and-courses&#34;&gt;Univeristy and Courses&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Building Construction Management &lt;strong&gt;Master&lt;/strong&gt; at the School of Building Construction of the &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://epseb.upc.edu/en?set_language=en&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Polytechnic University of Catalonia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (EPSEB-UPC) in Barcelona is a program designed to provide students with the knowledge and skills required to manage construction projects effectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The master&amp;rsquo;s program focuses on various aspects of construction management, including project planning, cost estimation, risk management, sustainable construction practices, and quality control. Students gain a comprehensive understanding of the construction industry, learning about building technologies, legal and regulatory frameworks, and management strategies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exams taken refer to the courses of:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Course&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Score&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Course&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Score&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Real Estate Marketing&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;10 / 10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;06.2023&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Models and Decision Tools&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;9.5 / 10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;06.2023&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Real Estate Management FM&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;9.7 / 10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;06.2023&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Management skills&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;9.5 / 10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;06.2023&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Process and Projects Management PMI&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;8.1 / 10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;06.2023&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Smart cities&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;9.5 / 10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;06.2023&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-career&#34;&gt;My career&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The choice to attend the Master’s degree at UPC, MUGE school, was driven by the reputation and academic excellence of this institution. The school offers a comprehensive and well-structured curriculum covering a wide range of topics in the field of &lt;strong&gt;REAL ESTATE&lt;/strong&gt;, allowing me to deepen my skills and gain a solid foundation of knowledge in various related fields.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In particular, I am drawn to the program’s focus on key topics such as Real Estate Marketing, which will allow me to learn specific real estate &lt;strong&gt;marketing strategies&lt;/strong&gt; and techniques. This will allow me to develop an in-depth understanding of the marketing principles applied to the real estate market and acquire the skills necessary to create successful campaigns and reach my target audience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, the inclusion of topics like Models and Decision Tools will provide me with a solid analytical and quantitative foundation for making informed decisions in real estate. I will be able to evaluate real estate investments, analyze risks, perform financial analysis and predict market trends using appropriate tools and models. This will help me improve my ability to make &lt;strong&gt;data-driven decisions&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;maximize real estate investment returns&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
